Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 1)
  - 1.42 PPWP Standing Committees
    - Budget and Finance Committee
      - 1967-1971 (Box 31, Folder 42)
      - Insurance Subcommittee, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 43)
      - Investment Subcommittee
        - 1970-74 (Box 31, Folder 44)
        - 1975-79 (Box 31)
        - 1980 (Box 31, Folder 45)
        - 1955-69 (Box 31, Folder 46)
      - Investment Subcommittee on Pension Funds, 1970-74 (Box 31, Folder 47)
      - Investment Subcommittee, Minutes, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 48)
      - Member Lists
        - 1967-74 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - 1975-78 (Box 32)
      - Mailings 1976-77 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Memos
        - 1973-74 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - 1975-78 (Box 32)
      - Minutes
        - 1970-74 (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - 1975-78 (Box 32)
      - Audit Subcommittee (Unofficial), 1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Special Budget Review Committee, 1977 and 1978 Budget Data, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee for Abortion Loan Fund, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on Insurance, 1977-78 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Reports, 1972-74 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Resolutions
        - 1974 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - 1975 (Box 32)
    - Community Affairs Committee
      - 1969 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Member Lists
        - 1970-74 (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - 1975-78 (Box 32)
      - Minutes
        - 1976-78 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - 1969-74 (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - 1975 (Box 32)
      - Suggested Revised Policy Statement on Population, March 17, 1972, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Education Committee
      - General, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Member lists, 1979-80 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Policy Statement on Education, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - 1.42 Expansion and Policy
      - Activities of the E&P Committee, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Organization, Reactions to the Report, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Reorganization, Report as Approved by the Board of Directors, 5/22/73, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on Organizational Structure, Minority Report, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on Reorganization, Final Report as Amended and Approved by the National Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Subcommittee on Reorganization, Report, 2/1/1973 (with Amendments), 1973 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Subcommittee on Organizational Structures, Cresap Report, July & September 1972 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Subcommittee on Organization Structure, Interim Report, 9/28/72, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Subcommittee on Reorganization, Minutes, 1972-73 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Subcommittee on Organizational Structure, John Robbins' Draft Guidelines, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Subcommittee on Organizational Structure, JCR Memo and Material for "Herz" Proposal, May 12, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Subcommittee on Reorganization, Statement, J. Robbins, 9/20/1972, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Subcommittee on Organizational Structure, Staff Comments on Robbins' Draft Guidelines, Sept. 1972 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Subcommittee on Regional Resource Centers from, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence
        - 1972-74 (Box 32, Folder 33)
        - 1975-77 (Box 32)
        - 1969-71 (Box 32, Folder 34)
        - 1968-1964-65 (Box 32, Folder 35-37)
      - Discussion Paper on "Causes," Policy, Program, and Allocation of Resources from Paul Todd, 4/24/1968, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Informed Consent and Confidentiality, Service Policy: Handicapped and Retarded, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - Joint Venture Task Force, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 41)
      - Service Committee, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 42)
      - Subcommittee on Comprehensive Health, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 43)
      - Subcommittee Dues Formula (Box 32)
        - Fair Share Formula, Amended February 1973, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 44)
        - Proposed Affiliate Fair Share Plan, 3/17/1972 and 5/31/1972, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 45)
        - Report, May 31, 1972, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 46)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 47)
      - Subcommittee on Federation Policy and Population Change, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 48)
      - Subcommittee on Future Issues
        - 1973 (Box 32, Folder 49)
        - Minutes, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 50)
      - Subcommittee, Margaret Sanger Regional Resource Center, 1970/71, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 51)
      - Subcommittee on Model Clinics, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 52)
      - Subcommittee on Organization from 1971, 1971-73 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Member lists
        - 1965-74 (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - 1975-78 (Box 33)
      - Task Force Conference in Education in Human Sexuality, Tarrytown, NY, 1974, 1973-74 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Expansion and Policy Committee, 1968-74 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Expansion and Policy, Minutes
        - 1974 (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - 1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - 1968-70 (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - Patients' Rights Task Force and Member Lists, 1973-74 (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - Statement on Patients' Rights and Responsibilities, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - Proposed Draft Policy on Sex Education, July 18, 1973, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Report from the Ad Hoc Committee to Study the Fund Raising Structure of the Fed., 1971 (Box 33, Folder 11)
        - Report of the Patients' Rights Task Force, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 12)
        - Revision of 5 Year Plan, 1976-1980, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 13)
        - Resolutions, 1969-72 (Box 33, Folder 14)
        - Report on Statewide Affiliates, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 15)
        - Specific Major Concerns (for 10/15/70 Meeting), 1970 (Box 33, Folder 16)
        - Talk by Eleanor Snyder Presented to Committee, 2/28/1970, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - Statement on Service to Minors, Comments, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Task Force: Education in Human Sexuality, Report on Conference, 1/26-28/74, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 19)
        - Task Force on Future Goals from 1973, 1973-74 (Box 33, Folder 20)
        - Task Force on Resource Pools, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 21)
        - Voluntary Parenthood, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 22)
        - Mrs. Frederick Romberg, 1966-68 (Box 33, Folder 23)
        - Policy Development Structure, Volunteer and Staff, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Finance Committee
      - Meeting, September 30, 1980, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Member Lists, 1979-80 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Minutes, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - ISA Finance Committee, Articles of Agreement, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - 1.42 Individual Rights Committee
      - Legal (Eve Paul), 1979 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 1968-80 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - Member Lists, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - Nestle Boycott, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Int'l Affairs Committee
      - 1973-74 (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - 1975-78 (Box 33)
      - Member Lists, 1975-80 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - I & E Committee
      - Correspondence
        - 1971-74 (Box 33, Folder 35)
        - 1975-78 (Box 33)
      - Membership lists
        - 1971-74 (Box 33, Folder 36)
        - 1975-78 (Box 33)
      - General, mimeos
        - 1972-74 (Box 33, Folder 37)
        - 1975-78 (Box 33)
      - Minutes
        - 1971-74 (Box 33, Folder 38)
        - 1975-78 (Box 33)
      - Membership List, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 39)
      - 6/3/1976 Meeting, Minutes, Report, Program, and Budget "10 Point Plan," 1976 (Box 33, Folder 40)
      - Minutes, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 41)
      - Media Subcommittee, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 42)
      - Media and Publicity Subcommittee, Minutes, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 43)
      - Public Affairs Subcommittee
        - 1974 (Box 33, Folder 44)
        - 1975 (Box 33)
      - Resolutions, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 45)
      - Ad Hoc, Subcommittee on Sex Education, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 46)
      - National I & E Advisory Committee, 1969-71 (Box 33, Folder 47)
      - Minutes of Meeting of Regional I & E Chairmen, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 48)
      - Communications Subcommittee, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 49)
      - Patient Subcommittee, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 50)
      - Population Dialogue Subcommittee, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 51)
      - Sex Education Subcommittee, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - 1.42 Joint Planning
      - 1969-74 (Box 33, Folder 53)
      - General, Mimeos, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 54)
      - Membership lists
        - 1969-74 (Box 33, Folder 55)
        - 1975 (Box 33)
      - A "Two-Year Plan" for PP/WP, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - 1.42 Medical
      - Activities, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 57)
      - Affiliate Medical Personnel Meeting, San Diego, CA, October 24, 1978, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 58)
      - Affiliate Medical Standards, 4/20/77, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 59)
      - Guidelines for the Elective Termination of Pregnancy (Abortion), Draft, 6/22/73, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 60)
      - Informed Consent and Confidentiality Service Policy: Handicapped & Retarded, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 61)
      - Invitations to serve
        - 1961-69 (Box 33, Folder 62)
        - 1956-61 (Box 33, Folder 63)
      - Introduction to Medical Standards for PPFA, May 31, 1977, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 64)
      - Job Description, Affiliate Medical Director, Guidelines, Formation and Function of AMC, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 65)
      - Medical Guidelines for Family Planning, A Draft Document, Task Force, Dr. Tyrer, 12/5/74, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 66)
      - Member Lists
        - 1970-74 (Box 33, Folder 67)
        - 1975-80 (Box 33)
        - 1955 (Box 33, Folder 68)
        - 1958-69 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - 1971 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Update of Addresses of 1970-1977 and PPFA Medical Directors, 8/79, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Standing Committees, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Memos and mimeos, General
        - 1978-80 (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - 1972-74 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - 1975-77 (Box 34)
        - 1964-71 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Memos and Correspondence, 1958-63 (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - National Medical Committee meeting
          - October 4-5, 1980, Denver, CO, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 9)
          - February 25-26, 1979, New York City, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 10)
          - October 22-23, 1978, San Diego, CA, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 11)
          - September 23-24, 1977, Denver, Colorado, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
        - Procedures for Regional Medical Committee, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 13)
        - Progress Report, National Medical Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 14)
        - Proposed Function of Research Subcommittee, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 15)
        - Proposal for Genetic Counseling, 1968, 1967-68 (Box 34, Folder 16)
        - Proposed Regional Medical Committee, 1970-72 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - 1.42 Medical Committee Minutes
        - 1979-1980-1975-76 (Box 34, Folder 18-20)
        - 1973-74 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Minimum Center Standards
        - 1956-73 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Nominating Committee, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Reports
        - Report to NMAC from Dr. Lippes, Use of Paramedical and Non-medical Personnel 1972? (Box 34, Folder 24)
        - Report of Ad Hoc Committee on Educational Promotion, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 25)
        - Report of Ad Hoc Committee to Review Research Programs in the PP Organization, 2/20/68, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 26)
        - Report of the Nominating Committee, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 27)
        - Report of the Program Subcommittee, March 14, 1968, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 28)
        - Report of Dr. J. Rovinsky, National Medical Advisory Committee, 1/7/70 to Exp. and Bd., 1970 (Box 34, Folder 29)
        - Report of Subcommittee, Medical Review Program, December 17, 1968, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 30)
        - Report on the Development of Examination Material in the Field of PP, 5/16/66, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 31)
        - Report to the Affiliates, Link Between Birth Defects & Progestins, 10/2/74, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 32)
        - Report to the Executive Committee, 5/18/72, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 33)
        - Report to the Medical Advisory Committee on the Training of New Professionals, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 34)
        - Medical Reports to PPFA Committee, 1955-66 (Box 34, Folder 35)
        - Member Resignations, 1963-65 (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Medical Committee Resolutions
        - 1970-74 (Box 34, Folder 37)
        - 1975 (Box 34)
      - Medical Standards Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Subcommittee: Abortion and Sterilization, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Abortion
        - 1974 (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - 1975 (Box 35)
      - Subcommittee on Endometrial Aspiration, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on Hormonal Contraception, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Public Health, General, 1959-67 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Publications, General, 1956-65 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee to Restructure Medical Department, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee, Sterilization Subcommittee, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Suggested Guidelines for Sexuality Education, Counseling, and Therapy, 12/18/75, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Syllabus for Preparation of PP, Physicians to be Clinicians in PP Center, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Syllabus from 1953, 1943-64 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Travel Reimbursement, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Task Force on Medical Audit, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Meetings, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Meetings, 1956, 1946-56 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Meetings, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Medical Council
      - Member Lists, 1956-60 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 1954-63 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - General, 1955-56-59 1955-1957 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Reports and General, 1955-61 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Statistical Conference
        - Correspondence, General, May 22, 1959, 1959-60 (Box 35, Folder 21)
        - Corrections, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 22)
        - Participants, May 22, 1959, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - National Council, Alan Guttmacher Inst., National Advisory Council, CFPPD
      - Ad Hoc Committee, Hospitals and Abortion, A Report, 10/13/76, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Agenda, 1975-77 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Composition, Appointment, and Tenure, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence and memos
        - 1974 (Box 35, Folder 27)
        - 1975-77 (Box 35)
      - Membership lists
        - 1974 (Box 35, Folder 28)
        - 1975-77 (Box 35)
      - The Institute's Future II, Report by the Long Range Planning Committee, May 1976, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Minutes of the Executive Committee of the National Council, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Memos, Relationship AGI/PPFA, 1974-75 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - Agenda
        - 1972-74 (Box 35, Folder 32)
        - 1975-76 (Box 35)
      - The Center's Future, A Report by the Long Range Planning Committee, August 25, 1973, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence and memos, 1970-73 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - Membership lists, 1970-74 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - Minutes
        - 1974 (Box 35, Folder 36)
        - 1975-77 (Box 35)
      - Minutes, 1969-74 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Procedures, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 38)
      - Resolutions, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - 1.42 Nominating
      - Correspondence
        - 1971-74 (Box 35, Folder 40)
        - 1975-79 (Box 35)
        - 1970 (Box 35, Folder 41)
        - 1967-69 (Box 35, Folder 42)
        - 1967-68 (Box 35, Folder 43)
        - 1962-66 (Box 35, Folder 44)
        - 1960-62 (Box 35, Folder 45)
        - 1955-61 (Box 35, Folder 46)
      - Mrs. Morton J. Baum, Nominating Committee Chairman, 1966, 1964-66 (Box 35, Folder 47)
      - Mrs. Stuart N. Scott, Chairman, 1967, 1966-67 (Box 35, Folder 48)
      - Nominees dropped, 1965, 1964-65 (Box 35, Folder 49)
      - Member lists
        - 1968-74 (Box 35, Folder 50)
        - 1975-80 (Box 35)
      - Memos, 1977-79 (Box 35, Folder 51)
      - Miscellaneous, Biographical Material, 1964-67 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - 1.42 Nominating Committee, Proposed Slates
        - 1980 (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - 1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - 1976-77-1974-75 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
        - 1974-1975-1951-60 (Box 36, Folder 7-13)
        - Slates, 1951-67 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - General
        - 1957-74 (Box 36, Folder 15)
        - 1975-79 (Box 36)
      - 1.42 Nominating Committee, Biographies
        - Gillespie, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 16)
        - Biographies for 1966, 1965-66 (Box 36, Folder 17)
        - Mrs. Morton J. Baum, '64, Rochester, New York, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 18)
        - Mrs. R. McLean Campbell, '64, New York, New York, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 19)
        - Mrs. Joseph Clark, '64, Nominating Committee, Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 20)
        - Mr. Harold Bostrom, '64, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 21)
        - Angela Bambace, '64, Baltimore, Maryland, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 22)
        - Mrs. Henry H. Clifford, '62, '64, Pasadena, California, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 23)
        - Mrs. O. C. Dobson, '64, Minneapolis, Minn., 1964 (Box 36, Folder 24)
        - Mrs. John Davies, '64, Princeton, New Jersey, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 25)
        - Dr. Johan W. Eliot, '64, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1963-64 (Box 36, Folder 26)
        - Mrs. A. G. Gaston, '63, '64, Birmingham, Alabama, 1963-64 (Box 36, Folder 27)
        - Mrs. John H. Gibbons, '64, Oak Ridge, Tenn., 1964 (Box 36, Folder 28)
        - Mr. Thomas L. Harris, '64, New York, NY, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 29)
        - Mrs. Lawrence Hart, '64, Dallas, Texas, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 30)
        - Mr. Meacham Hitchcock, '64, Cleveland, Ohio, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 31)
        - Mr. Henry L. Kotkins, '64, Seattle, Washington, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 32)
        - Mrs. Robert Lazarus, '64, Columbus, Ohio, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 33)
        - Mrs. Frederick Romberg, '64, Dallas, Texas, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 34)
        - Mr. Elwood Taub, '64, Portland, Oregon, 1964-65 (Box 36, Folder 35)
        - Mrs. John T. Watson, '64, Houston, Texas, 1963-64 (Box 36, Folder 36)
        - Mr. Charles F. Zukowski, '64, Birmingham, Alabama, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - 1.42 Personnel
      - 1977-1980 (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - 1970-74 (Box 36, Folder 39)
      - 1975-76 (Box 36)
      - 1966-67-1963-64 (Box 36, Folder 40-42)
      - Minutes
        - 1972-74 (Box 36, Folder 43)
        - 1975-77 (Box 36)
      - Member lists
        - 1972-74 (Box 36, Folder 44)
        - 1975-80 (Box 36)
      - Reports
        - 1973-74 (Box 36, Folder 45)
        - 1975-79 (Box 36)
      - Pension and Insurance Benefits Subcommittee
        - 1974 (Box 36, Folder 46)
        - 1975-77 (Box 36)
        - Minutes, 1975-77 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Public Affairs
      - 1980 (Box 36, Folder 48)
      - Projects, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - Congressional Contacts Questionnaire, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - Proposed Public Affairs Guidelines, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 51)
      - Member Lists, 1977-80 (Box 36, Folder 52)
      - Public Affairs Plan, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 53)
      - Public Impact Plan and Status Report, March 21, 1980, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Public Policy Panel, Joint PPFA-AGI
      - Minutes
        - 1978-80 (Box 36, Folder 55)
        - 1976 (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Resources Committee
      - 1969-74 (Box 36, Folder 57)
      - 1975-77 (Box 36)
      - 1974 (Box 36, Folder 58)
      - 1975-78 (Box 36)
      - Fair Share, 1980, 1979-80 (Box 36, Folder 59)
      - Final Figures, Fair Share, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 60)
      - Joint Solicitation Program, undated [1971?] (Box 36, Folder 61)
      - Member lists
        - 1970-74 (Box 36, Folder 62)
        - 1975-80 (Box 36)
      - Memos
        - 1974 (Box 36, Folder 63)
        - 1975-80 (Box 36)
      - Minutes
        - 1974 (Box 36, Folder 64)
        - 1975-80 (Box 36)
      - Long Range Planning Subcommittee (Draft of John Robbins' Presentation), 1975 (Box 36, Folder 65)
      - Final Report of the Planning Subcommittee, March 8, 1973, 1973-74 (Box 36, Folder 66)
      - Planning Subcommittee
        - Progress Report, March 15, 1972, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 67)
        - 1971-72 (Box 36, Folder 68-69)
      - Procedures to be followed in Demonstration Project, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 70)
      - Fair Share Plan: revisions and proposed revisions, 1975-79 (Box 36, Folder 71-77)
      - Resolutions, 1973-74 (Box 36, Folder 78)
    - 1.43 Advisory, Special and Other Committees
      - Ad Hoc Committees
        - Advisory Committee to the Chief Executive Officer, 1970-71 (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - Affiliate/Staff Committee, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Committee for Management, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Committee for Population Year 1974, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Committee for the Reorganization of the Medical Department, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - Committee for the Revision of the Standards of Affiliation, Minutes, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - Long Range Planning Committee, 1967-68 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - Committee on Abortion from, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - Committee on Board Affairs, Expenses
          - 1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
          - 1975 (Box 37)
        - Committee on College Affiliates, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - Committee on Committees, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - Committee on Educational Promotion, Report, 8/67, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - Committee on FPIA
          - 1973-74 (Box 37, Folder 13)
          - Interim Report, Sept. 2, 1973, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - Future of the Center
          - 1973-74 (Box 37, Folder 15)
          - Minutes, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 16)
          - Resolution, Relationship between the Center and the Federation, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 17)
        - Committee on the Future of the Community Affairs Department, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 18)
        - Committee on the Nature of the Presidency, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 19)
        - Committee on Reorganization, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 20)
        - Committee on Research Ethics, 1972-73 (Box 37, Folder 21)
        - Committee to Evaluate the Regional Structure, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 22)
        - Committee on UPPC, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 23)
        - Personnel Committee, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 24)
        - Committee to Evaluate the CEO, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 25)
        - Committee to Study the Fund Raising Structure of the Federation as a Whole, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 26)
        - Abortion Strategy Committee
          - 1973-74 (Box 37, Folder 27)
          - 1975-77 (Box 37)
        - Advisory Group, Population and Family Planning, Sex Education
          - Secondary Schools, 1966-68 (Box 37, Folder 28-30)
          - Member Lists, 1967-68 (Box 37, Folder 31)
          - General, 1965-68 (Box 37, Folder 32)
        - Affiliate Pill Purchase Committee, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 33)
        - Affiliate Services Coordination Committee, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 34)
        - Automation Steering Committee from, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 35)
        - AVS/PPFA Policy Committee, 1977-79 (Box 37, Folder 36)
        - Attorney's Meeting, October 14, 1970 and November 2, 1970, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 37)
        - Bequests Committee
          - Correspondence, 1967-73 (Box 37, Folder 38)
          - Minutes, 1968-71 (Box 37, Folder 39)
        - Bylaws Committee
          - Correspondence
            - 1970-74 (Box 37, Folder 40)
            - 1975-79 (Box 37)
            - 1955-69 (Box 37, Folder 41-42)
          - Member lists
            - 1967-74 (Box 37, Folder 43)
            - 1975-80 (Box 37)
          - Memos, general
            - 1969-74 (Box 37, Folder 44)
            - 1975-79 (Box 37)